you
So, I'm ready.
Enjoy. And loop. And let's warm up your cock. Up and down, up and down. Oh yeah.
oh yeah
that's jerk harder
okay
oh yeah
harder and faster
yeah yeah like that faster oh my god yeah
oh
stop
let's play with your balls
and now the balls
and the cock from base to tip
yeah
hard
now from base to tip very slow but hard
slowly but hard
yeah
Faster?
Yeah
Oh yeah, faster
5,4,3,2,1, stop
slowly
now on the tip of the palm
from base to tip, hard but slow
faster
oh yeah
yeah so hard
stop
do not cum
are you ready? for the last part
2, 1, go! very fast
oh yeah
step
go
fast
Stop.
One.
Go.
Fast.
Stop.
Go.
Two.
One.
Good.
Stop.
Go.
go
stop
yeah
you can cum
cum
yeah
oh yeah oh yeah oh oh i have 15 seconds to go if you're not wrong guys
10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1 stop
on the tip
from base to tip very very softly
That's all.